export const questionData = {
    BNU_Data: [
        {
            id: 1,
            question: 'Q1 - Tell me something about yourself. ( INTRODUCTION ) ',
            answer: `<p>• my name is Ravi Chachpara, I am 22 years old, I belong to Surat Gujarat I have been staying in Surat for last 10 years and I was born on 23 November 2000 <br />• I completed my S.S.C. (10th grade) in March-2016 from Gujarat Secondary Education Board in Gandhinagar and secured 45.86 % and I have done my H.S.C (12th grade) in March-2018 from Gujarat Secondary and Higher Secondary Education Board in Gandhinagar with 63.71%.<br /> • Then, I completed my Bachelor of Computer Application in March-2021 from Veer Narmad South Gujarat University and secured a 7.02 CGPA. <br /> • a after completing my bachelor I got an opportunity to work as Software Developer in TST technology Company which I took immediately and have worked from Sep 2021 to till today with complete dedication. And My Hobbies is Codding and Cricket<br />
        <b>Family details</b> <br/>
        There are five members of my family. My father's name Viththalbhai Mohanbhai chachpara his Job Working is diamonds, my mother name is Hansaben Viththalbhai Chachpara her work is homemaker, and my brother's name is Nikunj Viththalbhai chachpara his Job Working is diamonds and my sister's name is Rushita Viththalbhai Chachpara her work is a homemaker.
        </p>`
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            question: 'Q2 - Why are you interested in studying this course? <b>OR</b><br/> Why Choose this course <b>OR</b><br/> Why do you want to study this course?',
            answer: `The main reason for selecting this <b>Msc Cybersecurity</b> course is that it provides me with all the exposure I am looking for in its curriculum. 
        <br />•        Cyber ​​security is a growing industry with a high demand for skilled professionals A Master's in Cyber ​​Security can open up career opportunities  in fields such as security analyst, network engineer, and information security
               <br />•        The program prepares students for various industry-recognized certifications including CISSP, CEH, and CompTIA Security+
        <br />•        The program may include a core project that enables this students to apply their knowledge to real-world problems  Many graduate cyber  programs offer flexible learning options such as online and part-time programs
        <br />•        The curriculum is  updated frequently to keep up with the latest developments cyber security trends and threats.
        <br />•        The program includes courses for digital commuters

        <br />•  <b>Career Opportunities:</b> Pursuing an MSc in Cyber Security can open up a wide range of career opportunities, including roles such as security analyst, network engineer, and information security officer.

        <br />•  <b>High Demand:</b> Cybersecurity is a growing field with high demand for skilled professionals, and this trend is expected to continue in the future.

        <br />•  <b>Job Security:</b> With cyber attacks becoming more sophisticated and frequent, there is a growing need for professionals who can protect and defend digital systems and networks.

        <br />•  <b>Competitive Salaries:</b> Cybersecurity professionals are in high demand, which often results in high salaries and excellent benefits.

        <br />•  <b>Technological Advancements:</b> As technology continues to evolve, so do the security risks and challenges. Pursuing an MSc in Cyber Security will provide you with the knowledge and skills to keep up with these advancements.

        <br />•  <b>Variety of Roles:</b> Cybersecurity is a diverse field, and pursuing an MSc in Cyber Security will prepare you for a variety of roles within the industry.

        <br />•  <b>Multi-disciplinary Approach:</b> Cybersecurity combines principles from computer science, mathematics, and engineering, providing a multi-disciplinary approach to solving complex security challenges.

        <br />•  <b>Real-world Applications:</b> The skills and knowledge you acquire while pursuing an MSc in Cyber Security have real-world applications that can be applied to a variety of industries.

        <br />•  <b>Ethical Hacking:</b> You will learn about ethical hacking, including how to identify and exploit vulnerabilities in computer systems, which can help organizations to identify and mitigate security threats.

        <br />•  <b>Digital Forensics:</b> The program includes courses on digital forensics, which is the process of collecting and analyzing digital evidence to investigate cyber crimes.

        <br />•  <b>Risk Management:</b> You will learn about risk management, which is the process of identifying, assessing, and prioritizing risks, and developing strategies to mitigate or transfer those risks.

        <br />•  <b>Policy Development:</b> You will learn about the development of cybersecurity policies and best practices to protect organizations against security threats.

        <br />•  <b>Legal Issues:</b> The program will cover legal issues related to cybersecurity, including compliance with privacy laws and regulations.

        <br />•  <b>Industry Certifications:</b> The program prepares students for industry-recognized certifications, such as CISSP, CEH, and CompTIA Security+.

        <br />•  <b>Research Opportunities:</b> Pursuing an MSc in Cyber Security can open up opportunities for research in the field, allowing you to contribute to the development of new security technologies and best practices.

        <br />•  <b>Collaboration:</b> The program provides opportunities to collaborate with peers and industry professionals, helping you to build a network of contacts in the field.

        <br />•  <b>Continuous Learning:</b> Pursuing an MSc in Cyber Security is an excellent way to stay up-to-date with the latest trends and advancements in the field, ensuring continuous learning and professional development.

        <br />•  <b>Professional Growth:</b> The program can help you to develop valuable leadership and project management skills, which are highly sought-after by employers.

        <br />•  <b>Personal Fulfillment:</b> Protecting digital systems and networks from security threats can be highly fulfilling, as it provides a sense of purpose and contributes to the greater good.

        <br />•  <b>Future-proofing your Career:</b> Pursuing an MSc in Cyber Security will equip you with skills and knowledge that are in high demand and can help future-proof your career.

        `
        },
        {
            id: 3,
            question: 'Q2- Module Name',
            answer: ` <br />•        This course has been designed to prepare and develop your ability to carry out advanced analysis and research in the field of business within a global context.
         <br />•        Through the extensive academic resources in the program, including not only classes and lectures but also the industry links and practical experiences, I expect to emerge with a highly practical understanding of how to manage a complex business in the contemporary dynamic world. (Also please discuss the modules and explain one of them for modules, please use the university course link.)
         <br />•        the modules that are being offered by this course are very much standardized as per today’s market needs. All modules are .
         <br />•        Cyber Security Assurance and Risk Management - 20
         <br />•        Business Continuity and Cyber Resilience -20
         <br />•        Project - 60 
        <b>Some optional modules are</b>
         <br />•        Mobile and Information Systems Security Management -20
         <br />•        Cyber Security in Network Systems -20
         <br />•        Cloud Security -20
         <br />•        AI Based Security Systems -20
        Total credit points :180`
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            question: 'Q4 - Explain any 2 modules of your choice <b> OR </b> Module Details',
            answer: ` ➢ I am excited about the <b> Cyber Security Assurance and Risk Management </b>. One of Organizations implement cybersecurity risk management in order to ensure the most critical threats are handled in a timely manner. This approach helps identify, analyze, evaluate, and address threats based on the potential impact each threat poses. n short, cybersecurity commonly deals with vulnerabilities and cyber risks, while IT risk management commonly deals with how an organization's data, devices, networks, and assets are protected and managed <br />
            
            <br />➢  I  also look forward to  <b> business continuity and cyber resilience</b>. This can provide benefits that go beyond improving enterprise security  and reducing  risk  to  critical infrastructure Cyber ​​resilience also helps reduce financial losses and reputational damage. Experts in the field will tell you that cyber security is about protecting against cyber hackers who gain access to a company's network or attempt to access a company's information system and data When it comes to cyber resilience, experts define it as  a company's response to a cyber attack and how it will recover <br />

            <br />➢  I think I would find the <b>International Management of Finance module</b> challenging since I have not had much exposure in that field earlier. However I am very much interested in the module as I believe it would be beneficial for my future plans. Managing finance is especially important when any organisation reaches the expansion phase. So the contents of this module would play an important role as far as money management and financial decisions are concerned. <br />

            <br />➢  I am excited to learn about <b> mobile and information systems Comprehensive security  management</b>  is the process of protecting an 's data and resources from potential threats One of the main goals of these processes is to protect data confidentiality, integrity and availability Mobile device security means measures designed to protect the confidential information it stores  <br />

            <br />➢  <b> Cloud security </b>  ensures your data and applications are readily available to authorized users. Data loss is the most common cloud security risks of cloud computing. It is also known as data leakage. Data loss is the process in which data is being deleted, corrupted, and unreadable by a user, software, or application. <br />`
        },
        {
            id: 5,
            question: 'Q5 - How is the course relevant to your future plans? <b> OR </b> Future plans',
            answer: `Firstly , after completion of this course I will come back to my home country india as I have my whole family here, and I will apply to MNC [Multinational company] for job like Tata, Reliance, Hindustan Unilever, Infosys, Bajaj Ltd, Lulu Group etc..
            <br />
            Throughout this course, I will focus on developing solutions to real-world problems related to changing IT infrastructure and growing data volumes, as well as gaining a deep understanding of the underlying models and techniques, equipping me with the practical skills required to become a computer specialist. I will have the opportunity to work in Systems Security Specialist, Cyber Security Engineer, System Security Analyst/Architect, Security Analyst,and Systems Administrator. 
            <br />• <br />• 
            <br />•        Cyber ​​security is a growing industry with a high demand for skilled professionals A Master's in Cyber ​​Security can open up career opportunities  in fields such as security analyst, network engineer, and information security
        <br />•        The Master of Cyber ​​Security is a postgraduate study programme focuses on information security and digital technologies. 
        <br />•        It is an interdisciplinary field that combines principles computer science, mathematics and engineering 
        <br />•        The program is designed to teach students to recognize,analyze and mitigate security threats and vulnerabilities
        <br />•         Students  learn about various security technologies,including encryption, network security and intrusion detection
        <br />•         The curriculum covers both technical and non-technical subjects aspects of cyber security, including risk management, policy   and legal matters. The program usually lasts two years  and is suitable for university students must complete coursework and research projects
        <br />• <br />• 

             <br />•        There is a shortage of personnel with advanced skills in these emerging and growing fields, and graduates of this programme can progress to work in a multitude of roles and industries. This can be directed technology industry, related banking and financial sector or diverse ones such agriculture, healthcare, manufacturing and automotive. As a graduate of this programme, you'll have a solid understanding of the main disciplines that fall under these emerging and current areas. The kind of role you could go into includes:
            <br />•        Systems Security Specialist
            <br />•        Cyber Security Engineer
            <br />•        System Security Analyst/Architect
            <br />•        Information Analyst/Architect
            <br />•        Security Analyst
            <br />•        Security Engineer/Architect
            <br />•        Security IT Manager/Director
            <br />•        Systems Administrator
            <br />•        Network Architect/Engineer
            <br />•        CISO/CSO
            <br />•        Forensics Investigator.
            <br />  - This qualification is also heavily influenced by current research and developments that are at the forefront of the respective fields. It lends itself to a career in research and academia. Many of our graduates are expected to progress on to a MPhil/PhD and take on career in research and academia.
            <br />  -  After completing my Master's degree at a UK university, I will be eligible to work on a post-study work visa, which will allow me to gain international work experience that will help me secure a position at a higher level in MNCs in India such as IBM, Tata Consultancy Services, Reliance Industries, Microsoft, and other well-known companies. After I gained extensive information at this institution, it is more preferred for me to find a decent career in India. I am excited to return to my home country and continue my profession. After getting foreign job experience, I plan to return to my home country, and I feel that because I will have an international degree and experience, I will be able to find good career prospects. and My annual income will be 40-45 lakhs.
         `
        },
        {
            id: 6,
            question: 'Q6 -  After completing this course will you come back to india or what are your future plans? <b> OR </b> After Come back India',
            answer: 'yes , after completion of this course I will come back to my home country india as I have my whole family here, and I will apply to MNC [Multinational company] for job like Tata, Reliance, Hindustan Unilever, Infosys, Bajaj Ltd, Lulu Group etc.. ',
        },
        {
            id: 7,
            question: 'Q7 -  What job will you get once you complete the course? <b> OR </b> Get Job',
            answer: `There is a large scope of employment in different positions after this course like
            <br />•        Systems Security Specialist
            <br />•        Cyber Security Engineer
            <br />•        System Security Analyst/Architect
            <br />•        Information Analyst/Architect
            <br />•        Security Analyst
            <br />•        Security Engineer/Architect
            <br />•        Security IT Manager/Director
            <br />•        Systems Administrator
            <br />•        Network Architect/Engineer
            <br />•        CISO/CSO
            <br />•        Forensics Investigator.`,
        },
        {
            id: 8,
            question: 'Q8 - Did you consider any similar courses in the same subject area? ',
            answer: 'no this course Msc Cybersecurity is best suitable with my future plans ',
        },
        {
            id: 9,
            question: 'Q9 - Have you previously studied any other courses in this subject area? ',
            answer: 'My Previously studies is bachelor of computer application',
        },
        {
            id: 10,
            question: 'Q10 - What you have been doing since you last studied? ',
            answer: `After completing my higher education I was preparing for an abroad education.I was doing research on myself, my interest and what I  to <br /> 
        I was doing a job as MERN stack developer in TST technology  after my studies, I have experience 1.6 months now `,
        },
        {
            id: 11,
            question: 'Q11 - Why Choose this University?<b>Or</b><br/> What are your reasons for choosing this university compared to other institutions? ,<br/>a.	How did you find out about it? <br/>b.	What are the university’s most attractive features/achievements? <br/>c.	Why are these features/achievements relevant to your choice? <br/>        d.	  Is there anything unique about the university? ',
            answer: ` <br />•                  Buckinghamshire New University is ranked amongst the top 10 in graduate employability by the Higher Education Statistics Agency. This means as a student I will be gaining the right skills that any employer will be looking for. BNU has strong links with many industries, and thereby their courses are designed as per the industry norms.
         <br />•                  Class sizes are small and focused where students can interact amongst themselves and with the tutors for a well rounded understanding of the topics.
         <br />•                  BNU enables students to work on live projects from real clients thus getting a proper feel of the corporate environment.
         <br />•                  BNU is ranked Top 3 among the universities based in and around London for the Business related courses.
         <br />•                  BNU has invested £100 million in upgrading the facilities.
         <br />•                  The university offers high tech libraries which are accessible 24X7.
         <br />•                  BNU is ranked top 20 for student satisfaction according to the recent National Student Survey. This proves that BNU is a student oriented university.
         <br />•                  Moreover BNU’s Students Union has been voted amongst the Top 3 in the UK. Their program known as the "Big Deal'' offers many exciting social interaction and cultural exchange activities. And I read from the University website that this one of the very universities that offer students all student union facilities for free. This will give me ample opportunities to enhance my extra curricular potentials.
         <br />•                  BNU also offers great flexibility in accommodation contracts and the rates have been reduced owing to the pandemic.
         <br />•                  As an international student, these are some important factors for me to choose BNU
         <br />•                  121st in the Times University Guide 2023
         <br />•                  77th in the Guardian University Guide 2022
         <br />•                  Buckinghamshire New University was ranked 12th in the UK by the Huffington Post in a list of creative universities and was also included in a list of the top 14 creative universities in the UK by The Daily Telegraph. In addition, BNU has won awards for its training of pilots and music industry management.
         <br />•                  Location of Bucks New University- Business related courses are delivered in the High Wycombe (pronunciation: High WIKUM) campus of the University. Central London is easily reached from the High Wycombe Campus by train or bus. It is just 40-45 min away from central London. Can reach London Heathrow international airport in 30-40 min via train. As an International student, the location of the University matters a lot as far as academic and internship opportunities are concerned.
         <br />•                  High Wycombe is a large market town situated in Buckinghamshire county. It lies in valley of the River Wye surrounded by the Chiltern Hills. It is famous for its furniture (Chair making) industry. The place is well connected with the nearby cities like Oxford, Reading etc.
          `,
        },
        {
            id: 12,
            question: 'Q12 -  University rankings both for your chosen subject and overall ranking. ',
            answer: '121st in the Times University Guide 2023 <br />• 77th in the Guardian University Guide 2022  <br /> • Buckinghamshire New University was ranked 12th in the UK by the Huffington Post in a list of creative universities and was also included in a list of the top 14 creative universities in the UK by The Daily Telegraph  ',
        },
        {
            id: 13,
            question: 'Q13 - Which other universities did you consider <b> Or </b> Compare to Other University',
            answer: `I considered a few more universities which include University of Salford,<br />
        Teesside University, Solent University, and Greenwich University, De Montfort University (DMU) etc All these universities are offering Msc Cybersecurity with placement year. The course fee was also very similar.<br />
        One of the major reasons to finalise BNU was the quick response from the University. The management was quite helpful in guiding me through the entire process and making my admission process hustle free.<br />
        Secondly, the course structure at BNU seemed to be very impressive. I found some unique modules like  Cyber Security Assurance and Risk Management,Cloud Security and AI Based Security Systems Talent etc quite attractive. So, A good and efficient manager or leaders must be able to develop the capabilities of the team members, nurture their careers, and manage the performance of individuals and teams. Simply put, leaders are responsible for developing the talent in an organization. So, I strongly believe that this course will make me a capable leader who can formulate and implement strategies for the growth of organisation and effectively manage challenges in a professional manner.<br />
        Another reason was the location of the university. Like Salford and Teesside are almost 3 hours away from London. It will take 1 and half – 2 hours to reach Solent and DMU from the City of London. Whereas BNU is very close to London but at the same time it is not in Inner London.<br />
        Greenwich is located in Inner London- this means I will have to spend more for my living expenses. Also I found that the student satisfaction rate of Greenwich for business related courses is 82% whereas BNU has 90%. These are the reasons why I chose BNU over the other universities.<br />
        <h5 style= {{backgroundColor : 'yellow'}}>ALTERNATIVE ANSWER</h5>
        <br />●            I have researched about other universities such as De Montfort University, University of East London, Derby University etc.. However the modules offered are quite traditonal like more emphasis on project managemnt, HR management, marketing, finance management. Whereas BNU offers a more balanced mix of traditional and contemporary and innovative modules like organisational resilience, digital leadership, developing talents in organisation, logistics and operations etc. I found the course content quite futuristic and impressive.
        <br />●            I checked University of Bath and University of Wales also. They offer similar programs but their location is quite far away from London. As as an international student I prefer to stay close to London and experience it in all its glory.
        <br />●            I also researched about Brunel University however the tuition was quite high- which was around 21,000 pounds. So I didnt proceed with that option.
        <h1>ALTERNATIVE ANSWER</h1>
        <br /> Yes I have researched two universities in uk that is Greenwich university in this university my course fee is
        <br />19.5k GBP which is high compare to BNU .
        And the other university is Teesside university its course fee is low but it is very far from London so i didn’t adopt them so without wasting my time I have decided to study at Buckinghamshire new university .`,
        },
        {
            id: 14,
            question: 'Q14 - What is the source of information of your modules and university related research ',
            answer: 'for modules and university related research I researched following websites < br />https://www.bucks.ac.uk/  ( university official Website ) < br />www.timeshighereducation.com < br />www.QSworld ranking.com < br />www.mastersportal.com . ',
        },
        {
            id: 15,
            question: 'Q15 -  What are the near by places and town to your university ? IMPORTANT <b> OR </b> near places',
            answer: `- Buckinghamshire New University (BNU) is located in High Wycombe, England.  
        Some nearby places and towns to the BNU High Wycombe campus include: 
        <br />•	<b>Marlow:</b> Marlow is a town located about 10 miles southeast of High Wycombe. It is known for its picturesque countryside and historic buildings, as well as its selection of shops, restaurants, and cafes. 
        <br />•	<b>Beaconsfield:</b> Beaconsfield is a town located about 12 miles southeast of High Wycombe. It is known for its charming old town and close proximity to the Chiltern Hills, as well as its selection of shops, restaurants, and cafes. 
        <br />•	<b>Amersham:</b> Amersham is a town located about 12 miles northwest of High Wycombe. It is known for its attractive countryside and historic market town, as well as its selection of shops, restaurants, and cafes. 
        <br />•	<b>Maidenhead:</b> Maidenhead is a town located about 15 miles southeast of High Wycombe. It is known for its attractive riverside location and proximity to the Chiltern Hills, as well as its selection of shops, restaurants, and cafes. 
        <br />•	<b>Reading:</b> A large town located about 22 miles southwest of High Wycombe. 
        <br />•	<b>Henley-on-Thames:</b> A town located about 22 miles southwest of High Wycombe. Known for its boating and rowing traditions, charming town center, and various cultural and entertainment events. 
        <br />•	<b>Windsor:</b> A historic town located about 20 miles west of High Wycombe. Known for its stunning castle, charming town center, and numerous parks and open spaces. 
        <br />•	<b>Stokenchurch:</b> A small village located about 8 miles northwest of High Wycombe. Offers a peaceful, rural setting and easy access to nearby towns and cities. 
        <br />•	<b>Hazlemere:</b> A small town located about 4 miles southwest of High Wycombe. Offers a mix of shopping and dining options, as well as several parks and open spaces. 
        <br />•	<b>Wallingford:</b> A market town located about 18 miles south of High Wycombe. Known for its charming town center, historic buildings, and excellent transport links to London. 
        <br />•	<b>Watlington:</b> A small town located about 14 miles southeast of High Wycombe. Offers a peaceful, rural setting and easy access to nearby towns and cities. 
        <br />•	<b>Thame:</b> A market town located about 13 miles east of High Wycombe. Known for its charming town center, historic buildings, and excellent transport links to London. 
        <br />•	<b>Uxbridge:</b> A large town located about 17 miles northeast of High Wycombe. Known for its rich cultural scene, excellent shopping and dining options, and numerous parks and open spaces. 
        <br />•	<b>Slough:</b> A large town located about 20 miles east of High Wycombe. Known for its excellent transport links to London, vibrant cultural scene, and various shopping and dining options. 
        <br />•	<b>Aylesbury:</b> A large town located about 25 miles northeast of High Wycombe. Known for its rich cultural scene, excellent shopping and dining options, and numerous parks and open spaces. 
        <br />•	<b>High Wycombe town center:</b> Offers a mix of shopping, dining, and entertainment options, as well as several parks and open spaces. 
        <br />•	<b>Gerrards Cross:</b> A small town located about 12 miles southeast of High Wycombe. Known for its charming town center, historic buildings, and excellent transport links to London. 
        <br />•	<b>Waddesdon:</b> A small village located about 10 miles northeast of High Wycombe. Offers a peaceful, rural setting and easy access to nearby towns 
        `,
        },
        {
            id: 16,
            question: `Q16 - Why UK <br/ >1. Why do you wish to study in the UK rather than in other countries? <br />
        <b>2.</b> 	Why did you choose to study in the UK? <br />
        <b>a.</b>	What features/advantages attracted you to the UK? <br />
        <b>b.</b>	Is there anything that makes the UK unique? <br />
        <b>c.</b>	How do these features/advantages help your future plans/goals? NOTE – learn any 6 TO 8  points completely 
    `,
            answer: `UK is one of the most cosmopolitan and developed countries with a high HDI index and is known for its quality education and practical approach.<br />
        The UK institutions consistently rank among the best in the world and qualifications are internationally valued and recognized.<br />
        The British higher education system has been the basis for higher education standards around the world for a long time, with revolutionary teaching styles and modern facilities.<br />
        The UK is a multicultural country<br />
        As a student, I will get the opportunity to be taught by the world’s leading academics and experts. And last but not least the cost of education for an international student in the UK is generally lower compared to the USA, Australia and other countries<br />
        <br /> >1.<b>     High quality education</b>
        UK universities have an impressive international reputation and rank among the best in the world – did you know that four of the global top ten are in the UK? Research carried out by UK universities also impacts our lives every day, and is internationally renowned for its excellence. By studying in the UK, you’ll be immersing yourself in centuries of high quality academia.
        <br / >2.<b>     International students are welcomed</b>
        The UK has a long history of welcoming international students to study at its universities, and those who decide to study in the UK will be rubbing shoulders with some of the brightest minds from all corners of the globe.
        You will get the chance to mix, meet and interact with over 200,000 international students from all over the world, learning more about different walks of life in a place of contrasts and culture.
        <br / >3.<b>     Variety of courses</b>
        the wide variety of courses available for international students to choose from, whatever your age, ability or interest. If you wish to study subjects such as business, alongside hospitality and tourism in a dual honours degree, you can!
        <br / >4.<b>     High standards of teaching</b>
        UK universities are inspected regularly by the Quality Assurance Agency for Higher Education to ensure that they maintain the high standards of learning which are expected. As a student you will get the opportunity to be taught by the world’s leading academics and to be creative and develop skills sets and confidence.
        <br / >5.<b>     Shorter courses</b>
        Most undergraduate courses in the UK take three years to complete, and shorter courses means a quicker graduation and less money spent on things such as tuition and living expenses. Two-year degrees are an increasingly popular option, whilst most Two-year degrees last just one year.
        <br / >6.<b>     Scholarships and funding</b>
        All UK universities have multiple scholarship opportunities for students each academic year. Whether you have outstanding academic achievement or need that extra support to get through the academic year, universities will try their best to support you via funding (if eligible).
        
        <br / >7.<b>     The UK is an interesting place to live</b>
        
        With a mix of cosmopolitan cities and countryside villages, the UK is full of historical landmarks, famous music festivals, widely varied cuisine and amazing events to keep you entertained throughout the duration of your studies.
        
        <br / >8.<b>     Work while you study</b>
        
        International students who study a full-time undergraduate or postgraduate degree course at a recognised university are allowed to work part-time during term for up to 20 hours a week and full-time during the holidays.
        
        <br / >9.<b>     High rate of employability</b>
        
        Employers want high quality graduates who have specific skill sets, including effective, critical, and creative thinking skills. UK education is recognised by employers, universities and governments worldwide. Academic standards are of high prestige and the education will provide you with a solid foundation to boost your potential for having a higher salary and finding exactly what job you want.
        
        1<br / >0.<b>  Develop excellent language skills</b>
        
        The English language is of crucial importance in today’s global business arena. Employers want people with a grasp on English and there is no better way for you to learn English than to learn it in the country of its origin. You can immerse yourself and learn to live, work, and think in the English language, enhancing your employment prospects.
        `,
        },
        {
            id: 17,
            question: 'Q17 -  Have you previously studied anywhere outside of your own country?',
            answer: 'Ans – no I didn’t studied anywhere previously , outside india , studying in UK will be my first experience outside india',
        },
        {
            id: 18,
            question: 'Q18 -  Did you consider studying any other countries?',
            answer: 'no I didn’t considered any other country as after a precise research I found UK to be the best study abroad destination .',
        },
        {
            id: 19,
            question: 'Q19 -  How many countries did you research and why UK a better choice? <b> Or </b> Compare to Other Country <br /> <b>Or</b> Why do you wish to study in the UK rather than other countries?',
            answer: ` I researched and compared 3 counties which are USA , UK , CANADA . after a detailed research I found uk more suitable for me to pursue my further studies ans – as per my research studying in USA is costly and it is less safer than UK
        CANADA is good but climate there is so cold which is not suitable for people like us who live in semi tropical climate
            <br /><b>Quality Education: </b>UK universities have a strong reputation for providing high-quality education, particularly in fields such as engineering, finance, and law.
            <br /><b>Cost of Living: </b>The cost of living in the UK is lower compared to the USA and Canada, making it more affordable for Indian students.
            <br /><b>Cultural Similarities: </b>The UK has a large Indian diaspora and Indian cuisine, music and         art are widely available, making it easier for Indian students to feel at home.
            <br /><b>English-speaking Environment: </b>The UK is an English-speaking country, and a majority of Indians speak English, making it easier for Indian students to adapt to the academic and social environment.
            <br /><b>Visa Requirements: </b>The visa requirements for studying in the UK are more relaxed and flexible compared to the USA and Canada, making it easier for Indian students to study there.
            <br /><b>Strong Alumni Network: </b>UK universities have a large number of successful Indian alumni, providing a strong network of support and mentorship opportunities for current students.
            <br /><b>Climate : </b>The climate in the UK is generally milder than in the USA and Canada, which can make it more comfortable for Indian students. The UK has a temperate maritime climate with relatively mild temperatures throughout the year, and average rainfall levels. This can make it easier for Indian students to adjust to the climate, especially if they come from a warmer climate. Additionally, the UK has well-established infrastructure and a good public transportation system, which makes it easier for Indian students to get around and enjoy the local scenery and culture.
            <br /><b>Hence UK have both suitable climate and average tution fees along with affordable life style
            <br /><b>As living expenses is less than USA and CANADA`,
        },
        {
            id: 20,
            question: 'Q20 - Why did you decide not to study in india ? <b>Or</b> Not India',
            answer: `1. - A strong reputation: The UK has a strong reputation for first-class higher education and training and excellent research facilities.

        <br />2.  <b>  High-quality staff</b>Many UK academics are world leaders in their field and teaching and learning methods are constantly being developed to ensure high-quality teaching and learning environments for students.
        
        <br />3.  <b>   Flexible programmes</b>A wide range of flexible full-time, part-time and distance learning courses are available at undergraduate, masters and PhD level.
        
        <br />4.  <b>   Great Infrastructure</b>Another reason why studying in the UK is better than in India is the infrastructure or facilities available for students at universities. Most of them have state-of- the-art infrastructure and top notch facilities like computer labs, sports facilities, libraries etc.
        
        <br />5.  <b>   Quality Education</b>UK universities have a strong reputation for providing highquality education and research opportunities, particularly in fields such as engineering, finance, and law.
        
         
        
        <br />6.  <b>   International Exposure</b>Studying in the UK can provide Indian students with exposure to different cultures and perspectives, and help them develop a global outlook.
        
         
        
        <br />7.  <b>   Career Opportunities</b>UK universities have strong connections with international companies, which can provide Indian students with better career opportunities after graduation.
        
         
        
        <br />8.  <b>   Language</b>The UK is an English-speaking country, which can help Indian students improve their English language skills and increase their fluency.
        
         
        
        <br />9.  <b>   Research Opportunities</b>UK universities have cutting-edge research facilities and a strong focus on innovation, which can provide Indian students with opportunities to conduct original research and contribute to new discoveries.
        
         
        
        <br />10.  <b>Exposure to Different Teaching Styles</b>UK universities often use different teaching styles and methodologies compared to Indian universities, which can provide Indian students with a fresh and diverse learning experience.
        
         
        
        <br />11.  <b>Historical and Cultural Legacy</b>The UK has a rich cultural and historical heritage, with numerous museums, galleries, and cultural landmarks to explore.
        
         
        
        <br />12.  <b>Student-Friendly Environment</b>UK universities are known for their welcoming and supportive environments for international students.
        
         
        
        <br />13.  <b>Access to Financial Aid</b>Indian students may be able to access financial aid and scholarships to help fund their studies in the UK.
        
         
        
        <br />14.  <b>Global Network</b>Studying in the UK can provide Indian students with a global network of contacts and professional connections that can be valuable throughout their careers.
        
         
        
        <br />15.  <b>Collaborative Research</b>UK universities have a strong culture of collaboration, both within and between institutions, which can provide Indian students with opportunities to work on interdisciplinary projects and develop new skills.
        
         
        
        <br />16.  <b>Employer Recognition</b>UK degrees are widely recognized and respected by employers around the world, which can help Indian students stand out in the job market.
        
         
        
        <br />17.  <b>Diversity</b>The UK is a culturally diverse country with a rich history of immigration, which can provide Indian students with exposure to different communities and cultures.
        
         
        
        <br />18.  <b>Student Services</b>UK universities offer a wide range of student services, including health and well-being support, counseling, and career advice, to help Indian students feel supported throughout their studies.
        
         
        
        <br />19.  <b>Cultural and Recreational Activities</b>UK universities have a vibrant student life and offer numerous cultural and recreational activities for students to get involved in outside of their studies.
        
         
        
        <br />20.  <b>Innovation</b>UK universities are known for their innovative and forward-thinking approach to education and research, which can provide Indian students with opportunities to participate in cutting-edge projects and contribute to new discoveries.
        
         
        
        <br />21.  <b>Personal Development</b>Studying in the UK can provide Indian students with opportunities to develop new skills, gain independence, and build self-confidence.
        
         
        
        <br />22.  <b>Quality of Life</b>The UK is known for its high quality of life, with a range of urban and rural environments to choose from, and a vibrant cultural scene.
        
         
        
        <br />23.  <b>Access to Major Cities</b>The UK is well-connected, with excellent transport links to major cities like London, Edinburgh, and Manchester, which can provide Indian students with access to a wide range of cultural and recreational activities.
        
         
        
        <br />24.  <b>Global Recognition</b>UK degrees are recognized and respected by employers and academic institutions around the world, which can help Indian students to pursue further study and career opportunities globally.
        
         
        
        <br />These are some of the reasons why Indian students may choose to study in the UK instead of India.`,
        },
        {
            id: 21,
            question: 'Q21 -  Who is paying/sponsoring  your studies and how? Do you know their salary and where the funds are coming from?',
            answer: ` My father has savings for my education. So, I will be sponsored by my father.
            <br/>His Job Working is diamonds<br  />
        They have a annual income of 30 to 35 lakh and also they are saving for my higher studies for a very long time and they also have mutual funds and property in my name to support my study
        
        OR YOU CAN SAY I have a fixed deposit under my name of 22,00,000 INR i.e.22,000GBP that includes tuition fees and living expenses my fixed deposit can be liqiud at any point of time and there is no loan against my FD`,
        },
        {
            id: 22,
            question: 'Q22 -  What will be your living expenses while your stay abroad?',
            answer: `Mu Living expenses will be 13000(London) <br />10000 (outer London) pound's per year.(form BMU)<br/><b>Rent</b> : £100 - £150,<br /><b>Food and toiletries</b> : £35 - £50,<br /><b>Books and stationery</b> : £10,<br /><b>Laundry</b> : £4,<br /><b>Telephone and postage</b> :£10,<br /><b>Miscellaneous</b> : 	£10 <br />Total Weekly could be £175 - £230,  <br />Total monthly could be £700 - £920`
        },
        {
            id: 23,
            question: 'Q23 -  Are you open to part-time jobs?',
            answer: `No ,I will not do part time jobs in UK as my foremost goal is to study and develop myself <br />

        I am not going there to earn or work , I’m going there to study and also my father who is sponsoring me have enough funds to support my living expenses that’s why I do not have any need to work there .  `,
        },
        {
            id: 24,
            question: 'Q24 -  What is your tuition fee?',
            answer: 'my tuition fees for this course Is £16,600 GBP pounds per year.( and my scholarship  £1500 ).So I have to total pay only 15100',
        },
        {
            id: 25,
            question: 'Q25 -  How has your sponsor managed to provide you with this amount?',
            answer: ' they have a separate saving for my higher education which they started years ago',
        },
        {
            id: 26,
            question: 'Q26. Which English test did you take? If yes, what score did you obtain on your English test? <b>Or</b> English score',
            answer: ' I gave TOEFL etc , and my overall score is  103  <br />Reading : 30, <br /> Listening : 26,  <br />Speaking :21,  <br />  Writing : 26',
        },
        {
            id: 27,
            question: 'Q27 -  Are you currently employed?',
            answer: `Yes, I am currently job in TST technology as MERN Stack developer since June 1, 2021.<br /> Because I joined this job to enhance my knowledge and gain skills which I cant't gain from books`,
        },
        {
            id: 28,
            question: `Q28 -  Which accommodation will you prefer: a university dorm or private? If university <br /> dorm, then addresses of the university dorm. Where do you hope to live when you come to study with us? 
        <br/> Or <br />Where are you going to live during your studies?`,
            answer: `My first preference is university accommodation because As a campus university BNU is providing great accommodation facilities<br />
        BNU has two self-catering halls of residence in High Wycombe,<br />
        <br />
        <br />
        <b>1.  Hughenden Hughenden</b> Park Student Village is located approximately fifteen minutes walk away from the High Wycombe Campus. Rooms are either en suite with a shared kitchen-
        diner in flats of six, or studio rooms with a built in kitchenette. All rooms have a Wi-Fi and Ethernet internet connection.<br />
        <b>ADDRESS</b> - 4 Hughenden Ave, High Wycombe HP13 5GG, UK<br />
        <b>COST</b> - £139.00 TO 178 POUND PER WEEK DEPENDS ON TYPE<br /><br />
        <b>2.  Bro o k Street</b> Brook Street Halls of Residence are situated a five minute walk away from the High Wycombe Campus. Brook Street accommodation comprises of flats of between six and ten bedrooms; each flat shares a kitchen-diner, two shower rooms and two toilets. Each room has its own washbasin and internet access.<br />
        <b>ADDRESS</b> - Brook St, High Wycombe HP11 2ET, UK
        <br />
        <b>COST</b> - £82.00 TO 162 POUND PER WEEK DEPENDS ON TYPE<br /><br />
        providing over 800 comfortable single study bedrooms. All our residential halls are registered with, and meet the standards of the Universities UK (UUK) Code of Practice for the Management of Student Housing.
        <br />And until I found a permanent accommodation I will book a hotel before my arrival in UK`,
        },
        {
            id: 29,
            question: 'Q29 -  What is the source of information of accommodation',
            answer: 'my source of information for accommodation are BNU university website',
        },
        {
            id: 30,
            question: 'Q30 -  Will anyone be accompanying you at the time of travel to this country for the first time?',
            answer: 'no , no one is accompanying me at the time of travel , I will be travelling alone <br />In fact I am the first one in my family who will be studying out of india',
        },
        {
            id: 31,
            question: 'Q31. Do you have family or friends living in this country (uk)?',
            answer: ' no I have no family and friend in UK, I am first one in my family who is travelling to uk',
        },
        {
            id: 32,
            question: 'Q32 -  How will you be commuting to the university daily?',
            answer: `through public transport , bicycle or walk if my accommodation is near<br />

        As per my research public transportation system of uk ranked 11by TRAVEL AND<br />
        
        LEISURE in whole world which make it best for student to communicate to university on daily bases`,
        },
        {
            id: 33,
            question: 'Q33 -  What is your course start date?',
            answer: 'April 2023 -to April 2024',
        },
        {
            id: 34,
            question: 'Q34 -  What is the duration of your course? ',
            answer: `3 years if you are in bachlors <br />1 year if you are in masters`,
        },
        {
            id: 35,
            question: 'Q35 -  What is your passport number?',
            answer: 'my passport no is W0690587',
        },
        {
            id: 36,
            question: 'Q36 -  What is the average traveling cost per week?',
            answer: '0 to 140 pounds per month approx.',
        },
        {
            id: 37,
            question: 'Q37 -  What is the average accommodation cost per week?',
            answer: '120 to 170 pounds per week depends on type, size and facilities of accommodation',
        },
        {
            id: 38,
            question: 'Q38 - What is the student satisfaction ratio?',
            answer: 'University achieve an overall satisfaction rating of 85.5 per cent.',
        },
        {
            id: 39,
            question: 'Q39 -  What is the teacher-to-student ratio/Number of students per staff?',
            answer: ' 17.4 is faculty to student ratio',
        },
        {
            id: 40,
            question: 'Q40 -  What is the employment rate of the students graduated from BNU ?',
            answer: '98% of BNU graduate are in work or further study within 6 month',
        },
        {
            id: 40,
            question: 'Q41. What is your student ID/Reference Number?',
            answer: '219761',
        },
        {
            id: 42,
            question: 'Q42 -  Tell us the address of the campus of your university.',
            answer: 'Queen Alexandra Road, High Wycombe, Buckinghamshire, HP11 2JZ.',
        },
        {
            id: 43,
            question: 'Q43 -  When was this university established?',
            answer: '1891',
        },
        {
            id: 44,
            question: 'Q44 -  Who is going to come to pick you up at the airport?',
            answer: 'no one will come to pick me up at airport , I will book a cab to my hotel',
        },
        {
            id: 45,
            question: 'Q45 -  Will you be coming to the home country during your semester breaks?',
            answer: ` my return to my home country during semester breaks totally depends on my budget.<br />

        if I have budget which allow me to travel to my home country I will definitely came to india to meet my family and friends<br />
        
        and if I do not have budget to travel then I will stay in UK and focus on my studies and my personal development.`,
        },
        {
            id: 46,
            question: 'Q46 -  nearest station distance from BNU CAMPUS ? <b> OR </b> Railway Station',
            answer: 'The nearest station to the Buckinghamshire New University High Wycombe Campus is High Wycombe railway station. It is located approximately 2 miles from the campus and can be reached by bus, taxi or by walking. The station provides regular train services to London, Oxford and other nearby destinations.',
        },
        {
            id: 47,
            question: 'Q47 -  How much is the salary being advertised for these positions? Is that salary average for that industry/sector?',
            answer: 'tell them that after studying from uk I will be getting paid around 4-5 lakhs per month and degree from BNU will help me to get package which is above average',
        },
        {
            id: 48,
            question: 'Q48 -  When did you complete your previous studies? And what did you study?',
            answer: `I completed my Bachelor of Computer Application in March-2021 from Veer Narmad South Gujarat University and secured a 7.02 CGPA.`,
        },
        {
            id: 49,
            question: 'Q49 -  Do you have any family members that rely on you for financial support?',
            answer: 'no , my whole family is handled by my father no one rely on me',
        },
        {
            id: 50,
            question: 'Q50 -  Are any of the funds in that account borrowed from another source?',
            answer: 'no , this amount is saved by my father/husband for my higher studies only , hence it is not borrowed',
        },
        {
            id: 51,
            question: 'Q51 - What is your course level?',
            answer: 'NVQ level 7(National Vocational Qualifications )',
        },
        {
            id: 52,
            question: 'Q52 - What are the assessment and teaching criteria of your course?',
            answer: `Teaching delivered through mix of formal lectures ,seminars,tutorials,workshop Discussion and elearning packages,<br />
        Assessment is usually through a combination of individual and groupwork presentations elevators,pitches,eassays, reports and exams`,
        },
        {
            id: 53,
            question: 'Q53 - What are the famous places to visit in uk?',
            answer: `Ben,London eye, Buckingham palace ,Tower Bridge,st.James park ,st.paul’s cathedral etc.
                <br /><b>Nearest Airport</b> - Heathrow Airport
                <br /><b>Nearest city</b> - Halton, Bucland, Bierton
                <br /><b>University campus</b> - High Wycombe campus
        `,
        },
        {
            id: 54,
            question: 'Q54 -  Have you ever previously applied for any type of UK visa?',
            answer: 'no I haven’t applied for any type of visa this is my first time',
        },
        {
            id: 55,
            question: 'Q55 -  Near Airports',
            answer: `The nearest airport to Buckinghamshire New University is London Heathrow (LHR) Airport which is 16.9 miles away.
                <br /><b>Nearest Airport</b> - London Heathrow Airport
                <br /><b>Nearest city</b> - Halton, Bucland, Bierton
                <br /><b>University campus</b> - High Wycombe campus
        `,
        },
        {
            id: 56,
            question: 'Q-1 What is your Name, Date of Birth & Nationality-Passport Number?',
            answer: 'It gives me great joy to speak to you. My name is Ravi Chachpara, I am from Surat Gujarat,I have been staying in Surat for last 10 years and I was born on 23 Nov 2000. MyPassport Number is W0690587',
        },
        {
            id: 57,
            question: 'Tell me your family details?',
            answer: ` I belong to a middle-class family. There are five members of my family. My father's name
        is Viththalbhai Chachpara his Job Working is diamonds, my mother name is Hansaben VIththalbhai chachpara her work is homemaker, and my brother's name is Nikunj Viththalbhai chachpara his Working is Dimond  and my sister's name is Rushita viththalbhai chachpara her work is a homemaker`,
        },
        {
            id: 58,
            question: 'Tell me about your education background?',
            answer: `I completed my S.S.C. (10th grade) in March-2016 from Gujarat Secondary Education Board in Gandhinagar and secured 45.86 % and I have done my H.S.C (12th grade) in March-2018 from Gujarat Secondary and Higher Secondary Education Board in Gandhinagar with 63.71%. Then, I completed my Bachelor of Computer Application in March-2021 from Veer Narmad South Gujarat University and secured a 7.02 CGPA.
       `,
        },
        {
            id: 59,
            question: 'Where you will be studying?',
            answer: ' I will be studying at Buckinghamshire New University.',
        },
        {
            id: 60,
            question: ' Why not other universities in the UK? <b>OR</b> Why Choose this University <b>OR</b> why uni',
            answer: `- I have applied to only one university which is Buckinghamshire New University. Before
        applying to this university, I searched for two universities like the University of Sheffield &
        Newcastle University but because of tuition fees, I didn’t apply to these universities.<br />
        - As per my research, tuition fees at The University of Sheffield are £29,950 per year and
        £25,200 at Newcastle University but £16,600 at Buckinghamshire New University for the
        same course and also, I received a scholarship of £1,500.<br />
        - After seeing these points, I selected Buckinghamshire New University for my further study`,
        },
        {
            id: 61,
            question: 'How does your proposed course of study link to your previous studies',
            answer: ` I have done bachelor’s degree in Computer Application where I learned the principle of
        management, financial management, business statistics, and many more which will help me
        to study my preferred course. And I have also experience in the same field so it will very
        beneficial for me to successfully completed my course`,
        },
    ],
    UEL_Data: [
        {
            id: 1,
            question: `Q1 - Why have you decided to study in the UK and not in your home country or any other country? <b> OR </b> Why UK? <b> OR </b>Country comparison <b> OR </b> WHY NOT INDIA `,
            answer: ` <b> Why UK? </b>
     <br />->   There are many reasons to choose UK
     <br />•	Firstly, The UK is diverse country education in the UK is top in the world. the UK has a much better academic and educational system than countries like Canada and Australia. The UK has the world’s highest-ranked universities such as Oxford University, Cambridge University, and many more. It shows the education in UK is best in the world.
     <br />•	The quality of education in UK can be judged by the fact that as per the QS World University Ranking 2022, the UK is home to 17 of the top 100 universities in the world.  
     <br />•	A major advantage of studying in UK for students is the flexibility offered by the educational institutions. UK allow students to build their courses by combining subjects they are passionate about. 
     <br />•	Each university is subjected to regular inspection by the QAA (Quality Assurance Agency) to ensure that the government-set guidelines for learning, research, and teaching are maintained efficiently.
     <br />•	UK universities have strong research infrastructures.UK puts across 6.4% of global journal articles, 11.6% of citations and 15.9% of the world’s most highly-cited articles.
     <br />•	The main reason why I Choose UK because UK education system, which is really advanced and mostly based on practical knowledge and guidance. Also It is worldwide recognised.
     <br /><b>Country comparison</b>
     <br />•	Taking admission to UK universities is relatively simple and renowned for higher academic standards. 
     <br /><b>1. USA</b>
     <br />•	The cost of living and cost of education is very high. Like, University of Florida provide MSc in Computer Science course with 56,169$ tuition fee per yr.
     <br />•	Its two-year course. So, it will be hard for me to pay for my tuition fee.
     <br />•	In UK it takes only 1 year to complete master degree and fee at UEL is only 14750 GBP.so it will help to reduce overall study cost and accommodation cost also.
     <br /><b>2. CANADA</b>
     <br />•	The cost of living and Fee Structure education is Same. and 2 year course. Like University of Alberta
     <br />•	But UK CANADA is good but climate there is so cold which is not suitable for people like us who live in semi tropical climate so I am not preferred canada
     <br /><b>WHY NOT INDIA</b>
     <br />•	The Indian education system judge the students on the basis of their academic performance & not on the basis of their overall performance. The focus is only on the theory subjects
     <br />•	The study programs in UK Universities are well planned and designed to ensure that students get the best learning. This system encourages creativity, develops multiple skills, builds confidence, and enables students to think critically.
     <br />•	Nowadays, every employer wants people with a grip on English. And there is no better way for a student to develop language skills than to learn them in the country of origin. 
     <br />•	This will help me to enhance employment possibilities in India.
     `
        },
        {
            id: 2,
            question: `Q2 -What course did you apply to study and <b>why have you chosen to study this course at UEL</b> <b> OR </b> Module Name?`,
            answer: `•	I have applied Top the MSc in Computer science at the university of east London. Because this course is relevant to my previous studies.
        <br />•	  After completed my graduation. I started working in IT Company. As I have very much interested in technology side of computer activities.
        <br />•	  I have research about this course and see how Importance of this course in Indian market.
        <br />•	  This course is appropriate top me because it is not easy to get job in any of the IT companies in India with having normal degree, but after completed my 1 years in MSc Computer science I can be able to apply in any of IT Company in India with having an international degree.
        <br />•	  So, I want to Study MSc computer science in university of east London
        <br />•	  The structure of the course gives me the essential knowledge and skills for my future career.
        <br />•	  Because of some reasons like first of talking about course modules so I will learn five modules throughout the course of University of east London
        <br />->	  Which are : 
        <br /> 1)	Advanced Software Engineering
        <br /> 2)	Big Data Analytics
        <br /> 3)	Computer Security - optional
        <br /> 4)	Cloud Computing - optional
        <br /> 5)	Mental Wealth; Professional Life (Dissertation)
        <br /> - But three modules are that grab my attention.
        <br /> <b>1)	Computer security</b>
        <br /> •    This module aims to provide an understanding at the tools and techniques needed to protest computers, networks and internet sites from unauthorised intrusion.
        <br /> •    This will involve studding possible security risks and the application of appropriate technical, defensive mechanisms tools to counteract cyber crime
        <br /> <b>2)	Cloud Computing</b>
        <br /> •        This module provides me with an overview of the field of cloud computing its enabling technologies, main building blocks and hands-on experience
        <br /> •    The course will introduce this domain and cover the topics of data censors, visualization, cloud storage and various cloud paradigms.
        <br /> <b>3)	Mental Wealth; professional Life  </b>
        <br /> •    Conduct a practical project of a master level quality related to the scope of the selected MSc programme and develop skills appropriate top a senior computing professional.
        <br /> •    I will consider the ethical, legal, social and professional issues and the dissertation will require appropriate research, analysis design implementation, Quality assurance and project management. 
        <br /> 
        <br /> •	Ranking of the UEL is 801 in Qs world ranking.
        <br /> •	114 by complete university guide ranking 2022.  
        <br /> •	As per resech I found that uel is an internationally recognised uk university which currently has around 17000 students from 135 countries. enrolled.        
        <br /> •	Ranked as best modern university in London by national student survey
        <br /> •	2nd rank in the UK for teaching quality by times higher education young university ranking.
        <br /> •	UEL have a fantastic teaching staff, many of them are also leading researchers in their field, as reflected by the research excellence framework.
        <br /> •	UEL also have a modern, well equipped learning environment with modern lecture theatres & seminar rooms, a 24/7 library & learning centre 7 a multimedia production centre complete with audio & visual labs& studios. 
        <br /> •	Also provides a campus shop, bookstores, student union facility including a student lounge.
        `
        },
        {
            id: 3,
            question: `Q3 - What other UK universities did you research for the course you have applied for? What made those options less attractive than studying at the University of East London?  <b> OR </b> Other University`,
            answer: `•	 When, I short listed Universities to study International MSc Computer science in UK

            <br />->  I have researched other universities like  – 
            <br />1)	Bedfordshire University
            <br />2)	Coventry University
            <br />3)	Optional - University of Wales Trinity Saint David (UWTSD)
            <br />
            
            <br /><b>1)	Bedfordshire University</b>
            <br />•		This university is located at Luton England and this university has low ranked as per guardian ranking and also the study hour per day is lass as compare universality of east London
            <br /><b>2)	University of Wales trinity Saint David (UWTSD)</b>
            <br />•		This university campus is in London but this Course is not available so I am not prefer this university.
            <br /><b>3)	Coventry University</b>
            <br />•		601 rank is guardian university ranking 2022. So obviously the education value of Coventry is higher than UEL.
            <br />•		In this university the course modules which I personally Interested are not available
            <br />-		There are some unique modules in UEL like
            <br />1)    <b>Computer Security</b>
            <br />      Computer security, also called cybersecurity, is the protection of computer systems and information from harm, theft, and unauthorized use. Computer  is typically protected by the same means used to protect other valuable or sensitive equipment—namely, serial numbers,doors and locks, and alarms.
            <br />These modules will be very much use full in future because of nowadays security related issues like
            hacking and other problems which is increasing significantly.
            <br />2)    <b>Mental Wealth; Professional Life</b>
            <br/>Mental health includes emotional, psychological and social wellbeing, affecting our thoughts,feelings and behaviours. We want to use the term Mental-Wealth, as this allows us to focus on positive strategies and the things that we learn about ourselves to help us maintain our Mental Wellbeing.
            <br />
            <br />•	University of east London provides all course modules which I personally interested
            <br />•	 If me talk about the ranking of the university of east London. That the UEL holds 801st ranked as per the world wide and also holds 4.2 starts overall
            <br />•	As, it was for more affordable and was providing all the facilities that is needed for an international student to study in overseas environment.
            <br />•	It, also provides facilities like new Morden technology, 24 hours and 7 days library, sport club, student union, accommodation support, health and medical care or may more
            <br />•	on top of that when I compare the location of university. I found out that university of east London is situated in the heats of ok that is London
            <br />•	as per my opinion university of east London is satisfied all my need, that’s all reason why I attracted to study at the UEL as compare to other university
            <br />•	That’s why I selected UEL.
            
            `
        },
        {
            id: 4,
            question: `Q4 - In detail, explain how you expect this course you will be studying at UEL to help you succeed with your 5-year career plan? `,
            answer: `Throughout my study time I will developer lots of different skills for my future.
            <br />•	 This course helps me to further develop my knowledge and skills within the cutting-edge areas of computers science. The course has been designed to provide me with a blend of skills related to imaging technologies deployed industry and research.
            <br />•	 The course is thought and delicensed by leading researches who are actively angered in this rapidity changing filed to ensure that I am up to date with the latest Derailments.
            <br />•	 The flexible nature of the course will enable me to choose from a range of advanced modules that match my career ambitions. These include emerging areas such as big data analytics, artificial Intelligence machine vison, computers security and cloud computing
            <br />
            <br />
            ->	 There are many areas attar this course meaning these are also many different job opportunities after this course such as –
            <br />•	 Software Developers
            <br />•	 Web Developers
            <br />•	 Web Designer
            <br />•	 Computer Engineer
            <br />•	 Computer System analysts
            <br />•	 Information security manager or many more  
            <br />
            <br />->	 But, I would like software Developers
            <br />•	 According to topes, software engineering employment will increase by 22% by 2029 for software specialists.
            <br />•	 It is expected to increase at the fastest rate of all other professions combined. 
            <br />•	 I have to also have a deep understanding of various language or technologies, and ensure that I am handle my company’s work and services to the right people.
            <br />•	 One more thing, software developer play a huge role in the success of a company’s for ant into a global technology company’s market
            <br />•	 There tope, they are also paid according to the importance of their position and the average salary ranges between 8 t0 10 Lakhs in INR
            <br />•	 I will learn some more practical skills and team work. Which I could use in my future job and practical life.
            <br />•	 After, Completion my study, I will plan to return in India. And I will get job as a position at Software Developers
            <br />•	 I will get Job in many multinational company in India. Such as, Infosys, Wipro, HCL Technologies with the average salary ranges between 8 to 10 lakhs.
            <br />•	 After some time I Will also ret promotion as a senior position in my home country
            <br />•	 This all point will success me in my attar 5 years career plan.
            `
        },
        {
            id: 5,
            question: `Q5 - What is your future-plans? Please explain what your potential     roles, employers, and expected salary is after you graduate? `,
            answer: `•	 On a completion of my MSc Computer science course I will plan to return my home country India because my family is everything for me
            <br />•	 After coming back to my home country India, I will be able to find a good Positions such as - 
            <br />- Software Engineer/Developer
            <br />- Data Scientist
            <br />- Cybersecurity Analyst
            <br />- Network Administrator
            <br />- Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning Engineer
            <br />- Database Administrator
            <br />- Web Developer
            <br />- Mobile Application Developer or Many More
            <br />•	 As India is a developing nation, these are huge Opportunities and bid multinational companies are looking for skilled developers with international experience.
            <br />•	 Because during my MSc degree I would learn about hardware instalment and software development to troubleshooting and data analysis, having this all knowledge it will help me while doing job.
            <br />•	 In India, Digital and technology India project is currently running and it will help me to get job in Indian companies like Infosys, Wipro, HTL Technologies and this all companies will give priority to whom who have an international degree.
            <br />•	 I will be able to find a good job opportunities in India with expected salaries of 10 to 12 lakhs and 10 to 15 % annual increase and that I will be that I am currently making for my master’s studies in international computer science practices in 2 to 3 years.
            <br />•	 And also for my future : Overall a degree in MSc computer science from reputed university like yours’s  will developing my skills and It will allow me to gain an international experience and contribute this to my country..
            <br />•	 So, this choosing course will help me to more forward my career to the next level in my home country India.
            `
        },
        {
            id: 6,
            question: `Q6 - Living in UK? <b>OR</b> Accomodation`,
            answer: `•	 I will stay at student accommodation at university campus.
            <br />•	 Because it provides a well-appointed learning environment, including modern lecture halls and seminar rooms. It also offers a 24/7 library, Learning Centre campus store and bookstore, café, garden nursery, and student union facilities.
            <br />•	 There are two types of accommodation at UEL: premium accommodation and standard accommodation. Premium is expensive compare to standard. Standard accommodation divides in two category western Student hall and Eastern Student hall. 
            <br />•	 I find student accommodation in the western is cheaper and more convenient. Costs are 150 to 250 £ per week, £636 per month. It is located at the University of East London's Clare and Felix House Docklands Campus, 4-6 University Road, London code NO is E16 2RD.   
            `
        },
        {
            id: 7,
            question: `Q7 - Please explain your last qualification, what you have been doing since graduating and why you would like to study the course you have applied for now?`,
            answer: `•	 I did Bachelor of computer application from veer Narmad south Gujarat University in June 2021 with first Class with distraction and also I have some work experience in TST Technology for June 2021 to till date. As a MERN stake developer. 
            <br />•	 My decision to study abroad rather than in India is based on the fact that I will not be able to directly enter the workforce after receiving a bachelor's degree in computer science from any of India's reputable institutions; at Indian institutions, hardly any practical working opportunity is offered during the course that could help an individual acquire workplace relevant working skills. As a result, obtaining a bachelor's degree is useless in terms of gaining practical experience. Furthermore, a lot of criteria influence admission to Indian universities (caste-based reservations, for example), making it extremely difficult to gain admission to a reputable college or university. In light of these considerations, I chose to continue my education abroad.
            <br />•	 As I discussed earlier, I previously learned course related Software Developing, web application development and web design on a ground level. However, UEL gives me a real world experience in software developing, are studies and creates a good Data Structure
            <br />•	 UEL will help me to achieve a good skill by learning and attending comparable Technology using specialist software such as New Technology
            <br />•	 Overall this course will developed not only my learning skills but also it will provide me a real world experience in Technology level.
            <br />•	 I were learnt some found level of Technology knowledge, Data Analysis, Software Developing but UEL will gives me a one opportunities then I will leaned some advanced level of concepts in Big Data Analysis, Advance Software Developing. 
            <br />•	 The reason behind selection this course at UEL is to develop experience with the advanced learning technique in which I am lacking.
            `
        },
        {
            id: 8,
            question: `Q8 - . How is the course you have applied to study at UEL related to your previous qualifications and/or work experience?`,
            answer: `•	 Throughout my previous study in bachelor o computer application and I join MSc Computer Science Because I want to expand my knowledge in this field and explore my career opportunities. This are the reason behind choosing this course.
            <br />•	 After completed of my graduation I have gap 0f 1.5 year, but during this period started working as MERN stack developer.
            <br />•	 In this work experience I joined the knowledge of create successful programs and application, problem-solving. Write source code and many more skills
            <br />
            <br />->	 In this work my job responsibilities are – 
            <br />•	 1)	Work with developers to design algorithms and flowcharts
            <br />•	 2)	Product clean efficient code based on specifications
            <br />•	 3)	Integrate software component and third party programs
            <br />•	 4)	Deploy program and system
            <br />•	 5)	Troubleshoot, debug and upgrade existing software
            <br />
            <br />•	 And, also the software Developers overall role is hop closely with clients to determine what they need, then use programming language like JavaScript (Java or C++) to create programs
            <br />•	 Now I selected this course because after completing my graduation I had applied for a job in TST Technology Company
            <br />•	 And, with the help of my strong academic background and my knowledge I has selected as a MURN stack Developers in That Company
            <br />•	 As, After serving for 1.5 years in that role I fell that something has missing in my knowledge to dominate the IT Industry.
            <br />•	 And, to till that role of Knowledge
            <br />•	 I chose this course because it mostly relates to my current work experience as a software developer. UEL has the same course subject from which I can advance my Advanced Software Engineering and advance my career. As Advanced Software Engineering is a booming industry, I chose this course because it relates to my current job. In addition, this course has subjects like cloud computing and computer security.I selected the university because it offers courses in computer security, cloud computing, and artificial intelligence at the master's level. By taking these courses, I can deepen my understanding of these topics.
            <br />•	 So, I decided to pursue my master in this course on in this university
            `
        },
        {
            id: 10,
            question: `Q10 - Beautiful Places? - Himalayas`,
            answer: `The Himalayas are one of the most beautiful places on earth and my favorite place. As the highest mountain range in the world, the Himalayas attract millions of tourists each year. The Himalayas, located in Asia, span the following six countries.
            <br />India, Pakistan, Nepal, Bhutan, China, Afghanistan. This mountain range is known for its breathtaking beauty, rich culture and adventurous activities.
            
            <br />The Himalayas offer an unparalleled opportunity to experience nature at its harshest. Majestic snow-capped mountains, glaciers, and high-altitude lakes offer awe-inspiring views. The fresh mountain air, the sound of the wind blowing through the trees, and the breathtaking sunrises and sunsets bring you closer to nature than ever before.
            
            <br />The Himalayas are more than just a feast for the eyes. They also have a rich cultural heritage. The area has several indigenous communities that have lived in the mountains for centuries. These communities have their own traditions, languages ​​and lifestyles worth exploring. Local cuisine blended with local spices and herbs is also exceptional.
            
            <br />One of the most exciting things he does in the Himalayas is the adventure sports he is addicted to. From trekking to climbing, skiing to paragliding, there is something for everyone. The thrill of adventure, the adrenaline rush, and the sense of accomplishment after challenging hikes and summits will stay with you for the rest of your life.
            
            <br />In summary, the Himalayas are a paradise on earth and my favorite place. Natural beauty, rich culture and opportunities for adventure make it an ideal destination for those seeking an unforgettable experience. Think about the Himalayas the next time you plan your trip. do not regret.`
        },
        {
            id: 11,
            question: `11 - Favorite Color - Saffron`,
            answer: `<br />I would like to talk about my favorite color, saffron. Saffron is a warm, vibrant color that has always held a special place in my heart.It symbolizes strength, courage, spirituality and many other things.

            <br />Saffron is a color that has been used in many cultures and religions for centuries. In Hinduism, it is considered a sacred color and is used in religious ceremonies and ceremonies. In Buddhism, saffron is the color of the robes worn by monks and represents the simplicity and purity of their way of life. In many cultures, saffron was often used in expensive fabrics and clothing, so it is also associated with royalty and nobility.
            
            <br />To me, saffron represents strength and courage. It is a color that inspires confidence and determination. Seeing the color of saffron gives me the strength and motivation to try new things. It reminds us to be strong in the face of adversity and never give up on our dreams.
            
            <br />Saffron is also the color of spirituality. It is a color associated with the sun, which is a symbol of life and vitality. The color saffron is said to balance our body's energy centers and promote spiritual growth and healing.
            
            <br />In addition to its symbolic meaning, saffron also has beautiful colors. Warm and welcoming, it can add a touch of elegance and sophistication to any space. Whether in fashion, interiors or art, saffron is a color that never goes out of style.
            
            <br />In summary, saffron is a color that holds a special place in my heart.It represents strength, courage, spirituality and inspires me to be the best version of myself. Whether you love saffron for its beauty or not, it's a color that can bring joy and positivity into your life. Thank you for listening`
        },
        {
            id: 12,
            question: `12 - Favorite Food - Dhosa`,
            answer: `Dosa is a traditional Indian dish that is gaining popularity around the world, and for good reason. This delicious and nutritious food has many health benefits that make it a favorite among health enthusiasts.

            <br />One of the main advantages of dosa is its high protein content. Dosas are made from a combination of rice and lentils, which are excellent sources of protein. Protein is important not only for building and repairing tissues in the body, but also for supporting immune function and maintaining healthy skin and hair.
            
            <br />Another important advantage of dosa is its high fiber content. The lentils and rice used to make dosa are both excellent sources of fiber, which help regulate digestion and prevent constipation.Fiber also promotes satiety and reduces overeating. , supports healthy weight management.
            
            <br />Dosa is also rich in vitamins and minerals such as B vitamins, iron and calcium. B vitamins are important for energy production and brain function, iron is essential for carrying oxygen throughout the body, and calcium is essential for maintaining healthy bones and teeth. In addition to its nutritional benefits, dosa is also a low-fat, low-calorie food. This makes it ideal for those looking to reduce their calorie intake and maintain a healthy weight.Dosa is a versatile and versatile ingredient that can be enjoyed as a main meal or as a snack.
            
            <br />Overall, dosa is an excellent healthy food that offers many benefits to the body. High in protein and fiber content and packed with vitamins and minerals, dosa is a delicious and nutritious addition to any meal. So if you're looking to incorporate some healthy and delicious food into your diet, try dosas!`
        },
        {
            id: 13,
            question: `13 - Favorite Book -  How to Make Friends and Influence People`,
            answer: `"How to Make Friends and Influence People" is a timeless classic written by Dale Carnegie. His one of my favorite books on public speaking and interpersonal communication.

            <br />The book is divided into his four parts, each with its own principles. The first part deals with basic techniques for interacting with people, such as the importance of smiling and the power of gratitude. The second part focuses on how to get people to like you, including the importance of genuinely caring and actively listening to others. The third part is about how you can convince people of your point of view using principles such as avoiding arguments and respecting the opinions of others. Finally, Part 4 deals with leadership. There are such principles as inspiring others and showing honor where honor is.
            
           <br /> One of the main reasons I like this book is its practicality. The principles are easy to understand, applicable to everyday life, and can have a profound impact on how you communicate and relate to others. For example, one principle that sticks with me is the importance of using a person's name when speaking to them. This simple technique makes the other person feel valued and respected and helps build a stronger connection.
            
            <br />Another reason I love this book is the emphasis on empathy and understanding. The principle is not just manipulating others to get what you want, but genuinely caring about others and trying to understand their point of view. This is an important aspect of communicating effectively and building strong relationships.`
        },
        {
            id: 14,
            question: `Q14 - Favorite Flower - Rose`,
            answer: `Beauty: Roses are known for their stunning beauty and come in a variety of colors, shapes, and sizes. They are often used in floral arrangements, gardens, and as a symbol of love and romance.

            <br />Fragrance: Many varieties of roses have a delightful scent, which can be enjoyed both in the garden and in the home.
            
            <br />Symbolism: Roses have been used as a symbol for various emotions and occasions, such as love, passion, friendship, gratitude, and sympathy.
            
            <br />Health benefits: Roses contain antioxidants and other beneficial compounds that may help improve skin health, reduce inflammation, and boost the immune system.
            
            <br />Easy to grow: Many types of roses are relatively easy to grow, making them a popular choice for home gardeners.
            
            <br />Overall, whether you choose a rose for its beauty, fragrance, symbolism, health benefits, or ease of growing, there are plenty of good reasons to add this lovely flower to your life.`
        }
    ]
}